[
  {
    "id": "18",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Data where we already know what the target attribute is",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["labeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "19",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Data that has been collected with no target attribute",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unlabeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "20",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Supervised learning is mostly used with  ______",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["labeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "21",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Unsupervised learning is mostly used with  ______",
      "answers": [
        "labeled data",
        "unlabeled data",
        "formatted data",
        "unformatted data"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["unlabeled data"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "22",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which describe the categorical feature type?",
      "answers": [
        "associated with a group",
        "qualitative",
        "discrete",
        "expressed as a measurable number",
        "quantitative",
        "infinite in number"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["associated with a group",
        "qualitative",
        "discrete"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "23",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 3",
      "question": "Which describe the continuous feature type?",
      "answers": [
        "associated with a group",
        "qualitative",
        "discrete",
        "expressed as a measurable number",
        "quantitative",
        "infinite in number"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["expressed as a measurable number",
        "quantitative",
        "infinite in number"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "24",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Text data is ______ data",
      "answers": [
        "corpus",
        "qualitative",
        "discrete",
        "quantitative"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["corpus"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "25",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ datasets refers to factual data that has been observed or measured, has been successfully labeled",
      "answers": [
        "ground truth",
        "qualitative",
        "discrete",
        "quantitative"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["ground truth"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "26",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A tool that helps build ground truth datasets by allowing different types of tagging/labeling processes",
      "answers": [
        "SageMaker Ground Truth",
        "Amazon Streams",
        "SageMaker Jupyter Notebooks",
        "SageMaker Hosting Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["SageMaker Ground Truth"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "27",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "As of September 2020, new path for S3 is ______",
      "answers": [
        "https://bucketname.s3.amazonaws.com/",
        "https://s3.bucketname.amazonaws.com/",
        "https://amazonaws.bucketname.s3.com/",
        "https://bucketname.regionname.s3.amazonaws.com/"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["https://bucketname.s3.amazonaws.com/"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "28",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ allows you to query data directly from S3",
      "answers": [
        "Redshift Spectrum",
        "Kinesis Data Streams",
        "Kinesis Data Firehose",
        "Elastic Map Reduce cluster"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Redshift Spectrum"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "29",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Managed time-series data store",
      "answers": [
        "Redshift",
        "Timestream",
        "DocumentDB",
        "DynamoDB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Timestream"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "30",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Place to migrate MongoDB data",
      "answers": [
        "Redshift",
        "Timestream",
        "DocumentDB",
        "DynamoDB"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DocumentDB"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "31",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Transfer data from on prem to AWS, or between AWS services",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "32",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Uses activity types, for example CopyActivity, EmrActivity, etc.",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "33",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can also be used as a transformation resource",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "34",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Migrate data between different databases, or output results onto S3",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DMS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "35",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can do heterogeneous migration or homogeneous",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DMS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "36",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Does not do transformation",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["DMS"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "37",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Managed ETL service",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "38",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Creates table in a data catalog using metadata",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "39",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Craws the data to determine the schema of the data",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "40",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Uses classifiers to identify the schema for your data",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "41",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can create custom classifier using this service",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "42",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can move data from S3, DynamoDB, RDS, RedShift, Database on EC2 to Athena, EMR, S3, Redshift",
      "answers": [
        "Data Pipeline",
        "DMS",
        "Glue",
        "EMR"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "43",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "With Glue which of these are NOT a valid output format?",
      "answers": [
        "avro",
        "csv",
        "ion",
        "groklog",
        "json",
        "orc",
        "parquet",
        "xml",
        "protobuf"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["protobuf"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "44",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Managed hadoop cluster ecosystem that runs on multiple EC2 instances",
      "answers": [
        "EMR",
        "ECS",
        "Athena",
        "EKS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EMR"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "45",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Run distributed workloads over many EC2 instances using many tools (Spark, Hive, presto, TensorFlow, mxnet, jupyter, etc.) processing petabytes of data",
      "answers": [
        "EMR",
        "ECS",
        "Athena",
        "EKS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EMR"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "46",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Serverless platform that allows you to run sql queries on your S3 data",
      "answers": [
        "EMR",
        "ECS",
        "Athena",
        "EKS"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Athena"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "47",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which is NOT a difference between Redshift Spectrum and Athena",
      "answers": [
        "Both query S3 data",
        "Athena does not need a Redshift cluster",
        "Athena is for customers who do not have Redshift or do not want to use it to quickly query S3 data",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["None of the above"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "48",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool should you use when migrating a PostgreSQL instance with training data?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "49",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool should you use when migrating unstructured log files in S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "50",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 2",
      "question": "Which migration tool should you use when migrating clustered Redshift data?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "51",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool should you use when migrating an on-premise MySQL instance with training data?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Migration Service"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "52",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool do you use when migrating by specifying a SQLActivity query and placing the output to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "53",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool do you use when migrating by creating a custom classifier and outputting the results to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "54",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool do you use when migrating by using the unload command to return the results of a query to a CSV file in S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Pipeline"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "55",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Which migration tool do you use when migrating by creating a data catalog describing data and loading it into S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Glue"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "56",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "Data Collection",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "______ can load data in CSV format to S3?",
      "answers": [
        "AWS Data Pipeline",
        "AWS Glue",
        "AWS Data Migration Service"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["AWS Data Migration Service"]
    }
  }
]